

MD. AL-AMIN Full Stack Web Developer

LANGUAGE SKILL

ENGLISH BANGLA HINDI



KEY SKILLS

- Front-end development
- Back-end development
- Database management
- Web architecture
- Version control
- Problem-solving ability
- Time management

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS

- Member, Dhaka Commerce College Programming Club.
- Member, Shikhbe Shobai Institute Batch 575.

<u> www.alamingithub.com</u>

ABOUT ME

Myself Alamin Talukder. I am a Full Stack Web Designer & Developer. Currently A CSE Student Of Dhaka Commerce College Affiliated National University. I have a 5+ years of Experience in Designing and and Developing Website. Developed Dynamic & Interactive Website That Ensured High Traffic, Page Views & User Experience.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Web Developer •

Shikhbe Shobai | January 2024 - june 2024

Graphics Designer •

Shahin Telecom | March 2023 - December 2023

Web Developer •

Banglaverse Network | June 2020 - Present

EDUCATION

(2023 - Present) National University •

Computer Science & Engineering

(2020 - 2022) B.C.I.C School & College •

Science

CERTIFICATIONS

- Full Stack Web Developer Certified •
- C Language Programmer Certified
 - **Graphics Designer Certification**
 - UI / UX Designer Certification •

+880 1560 049232



Shuvojar73@gmail.com 🔀

